let questions = [
    {
    num: 1,
    question: "Under which of the following Android is licensed?",
    answer: "MIT",
    options: [
      "OSS",
      "Sourcefog",
      "MIT",
      "Non"
    ]
  },
  {
    num: 2,
    question: "Does android support other languages than java??",
    answer: "Yes",
    options: [
      "No",
      "Maybe",
      "Yes",
      "Non"
    ]
  },
  {
    num: 3,
    question: "For which of the following Android is mainly developed?",
    answer: "Mobile device",
    options: [
      "Severs",
      "Mobile device",
      "Laptop",
      "T-Mobile"
    ]
  },

  {
    num: 4,
    question: "What does XML stand for?",
    answer: "eXtensible Markup Language",
    options: [
      "eXTra Multi-Program Language",
      "eXecutable Multiple Language",
      "eXtensible Markup Language",
      "eXamine Multiple Language"
    ]
  },
  {
    num: 5,
    question: "What does SQLite?",
    answer: "Local Database",
    options: [
      "Statement Question Language",
      "Stylesheet Query Language",
      "Stylish Question Language",
      "Local Database"
    ]
  },


  {
    num: 6,
    question: "Android is based on which of the following language?",
    answer: "Java",
    options: [
      "C",
      "C++",
      "Java",
      "Non"
    ]
  },


  {
    num: 7,
    question: "Which of the following android version is named Jelly Bean?",
    answer: "4.1",
    options: [
      "3.1",
      "4.1",
      "2.1",
      "1.1"
    ]
  },


  {
    num: 8,
    question: "Which of the following is the API level of Android version 5.0?",
    answer: "21",
    options: [
      "21",
      "22",
      "23",
      "24"
    ]
  },



  {
    num: 9,
    question: "In which year OHA (Open Handset Alliance) is announced?",
    answer: "2007",
    options: [
      "2005",
      "2006",
      "2007",
      "2008"
    ]
  },



  {
    num: 10,
    question: "Which of the following virtual machine is used by the Android?",
    answer: "Dalvic",
    options: [
      "JVM",
      "Dalvic",
      "SDK",
      "JDK"
    ]
  },





 

  


];